Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- NBC Corporate – People
  - People
    - Snyder, Tom (Box 41, Folder 15.)
    - Stabile, James A. (Box 41, Folder 16.)
    - Stanley, Ed, 1967; 1978 (Box 41, Folder 17.)
    - Stanley, Ed – Memorial service with remarks by Julian Goodman, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 18.)
    - Stanley, Ed – Memorial service, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 19.)
    - Stanton, Frank (Box 41, Folder 20.)
    - Stindt, Gary, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 21.)
    - Stone, Robert L. (Box 41, Folder 22.)
    - Swayze, John Cameron (Box 41, Folder 23.)
    - Taishoff, Sol. (Box 41, Folder 24.)
    - Taylor, Davidson (Box 41, Folder 25.)
    - Tebet, David/John Wayne (Box 41, Folder 26.)
    - Teitelbaum, David (Box 41, Folder 27.)
    - Tempone, Joe (Box 41, Folder 28.)
    - Tinker, Grant (Box 41, Folder 29.)
    - Tornabene, Russell C. (mention of Tippy Huntley) (Box 41, Folder 30.)
  - People
    - Trammell, Niles (Box 42, Folder 1.)
    - Traviesas, Hermino (Box 42, Folder 2.)
    - Vanocur, Sander (Box 42, Folder 3.)
    - Vicas, George, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 4.)
    - Wald, Richard, 1974-1979 (Box 42, Folder 5.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – Appointment at NBC news, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 6.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – President NBC news, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 7.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – President NBC news, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 8.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – President NBC news, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 9.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – President NBC news, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 10.)
    - Wald, Richard C. – President NBC news, 1977-1986 (Box 42, Folder 11.)
    - Walters, Barbara, 1971-1976 (Box 42, Folder 12.)
    - Walters, Barbara (Box 42, Folder 13.)
    - Walters, Barbara (Box 42, Folder 14.)
    - Walworth, Ted (President) (Box 42, Folder 15.)
    - Walworth, Theodore H. (Box 42, Folder 16.)
    - Weaver, Sylvester L., Jr. (Box 42, Folder 17.)
    - Welpott, Ray W. (President NBC TV Stations), 1971 – Retirement (Box 42, Folder 18.)
    - Welch, Jack (GE Chairman) (Box 42, Folder 19.)
    - Werner, Robert (RCA) (Box 42, Folder 20.)
    - Who’s Who in NBC News, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 21.)
    - Wilson, Flip (Box 42, Folder 22.)
    - Wolzien, Thomas R. (Box 42, Folder 23.)
    - Wood, Bob (Box 42, Folder 24.)
    - Wright, Robert C. (Chairman of NBC), 1986 (Box 42, Folder 25.)
    - Yates, Ted, 1966- 1967 (Box 42, Folder 26.)
    - Yates, Ted, 1967; News of his death and tributes (Box 42, Folder 27.)
    - Yates, Ted, 1967; news and tributes at his death (Box 42, Folder 28.)
    - Yates, Ted – Script – “The Documentaries of Ted Yates”, August 6, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 29.)
    - Yates, Ted – Typescript The Long, March – May 1967 with correspondence (Box 42, Folder 30.)
- NBC Corporate – Personal
  - Personal – Correspondence
    - Adams - Ashley (Box 43, Folder 1.)
    - Bagshaw - Boccardi (Box 43, Folder 2.)
    - Clyne – Chatsworth Avenue School (Box 43, Folder 3.)
    - Dorf - Durante (Box 43, Folder 4.)
    - Eisenhower (Box 43, Folder 5.)
    - Farrell - Freeman (Box 43, Folder 6.)
    - Gaines – Grimm (Box 43, Folder 7.)
    - Hamilton – Huddleston (Box 43, Folder 8.)
    - Jackson (Box 43, Folder 9.)
    - Kintner (Box 43, Folder 10.)
    - Laricci (Box 43, Folder 11.)
    - Muir – Museum of Broadcasting (Box 43, Folder 12.)
    - Nixon – New York Jets Football Club (Box 43, Folder 13.)
    - OdorizzI (Box 43, Folder 14.)
    - Paley – Pennybacker (Box 43, Folder 15.)
    - Read – Rylander (Box 43, Folder 16.)
    - Scanlon – Sullivan (Box 43, Folder 17.)
    - Television Academy Hall of Fame – Tomlinson (Box 43, Folder 18.)
    - U – V (Box 43, Folder 19.)
    - Wassaman – Windows (Box 43, Folder 20.)
    - Yergin (Box 43, Folder 21.)
    - unidentified (Box 43, Folder 22.)
  - Personal – Invitations
    - London reception, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 1.)
    - People’s Republic of China, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2.)
    - Republican dinner, February 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3.)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 4.)
    - January 1978 (Box 44, Folder 5.)
    - February 1978 (Box 44, Folder 6.)
    - March 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7.)
    - April 1978 (Box 44, Folder 8.)
    - May 1978 (Box 44, Folder 9.)
    - June 1978 (Box 44, Folder 10.)
    - July 1978 (Box 44, Folder 11.)
    - August 1978 (Box 44, Folder 12.)
    - September 1978 (Box 44, Folder 13.)
    - October 1978 (Box 44, Folder 14.)
    - November 1978 (Box 44, Folder 15.)
    - March 1979 (Box 44, Folder 16.)
    - Christmas Cards (Box 44, Folder 17.)
  - Personal – Articles about Julian Goodman
    - 1954 – 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1.)
    - 1961 (Box 45, Folder 2.)
    - Press releases, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 3.)
    - 1962 (Box 45, Folder 4.)
    - 1963- 1964 (Box 45, Folder 5.)
    - Press releases, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 6.)
    - 1965 (Box 45, Folder 7.)
    - Press releases, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 8.)
    - 1966 (Box 45, Folder 9.)
    - 1966 (Box 45, Folder 10.)
    - Press releases, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 11.)
    - Sponsor: the Magazine of Broadcast Advertising, May 16, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 12.)
    - “Why Julian Goodman?” in The Beam, July 1966 (Box 45, Folder 13.)
    - 1967 (Box 45, Folder 14.)
    - 1968 (Box 45, Folder 15.)
    - Press releases, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 16.)
    - 1969 (Box 45, Folder 17.)
    - Press releases, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 18.)
    - 1970 (Box 45, Folder 19.)
    - Press releases, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 20.)
    - 1971 (Box 45, Folder 21.)
    - 1972 (Box 45, Folder 22.)
  - Personal – Articles about Julian Goodman
    - Press releases, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1.)
    - “A Long Way from Glasgow” in Insight, June 2, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 2.)
    - 1973 (Box 46)
    - “Enemies List” in Sunday Times Magazine, pp. 14 – 17, August 19, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4.)
    - “The Chosen Few”(The Enemy List) in Of Westchester, September/October 1973 (Box 46, Folder 5.)
    - 1974 (Box 46, Folder 6.)
    - press releases –JG becomes Chairman of NBC, April 1974 (Box 46, Folder 7.)
    - press releases, April 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8.)
    - 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9.)
    - New York Magazine (p. 46), May 12, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10.)
    - press releases –Sigma Delta Chi, Fall 1975 (Box 46, Folder 11.)
    - “Three to the Top” by Jimmy Lowe, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 12.)
    - press releases, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 13.)
    - 1976 (Box 46, Folder 14.)
    - “NBC Boss Gets the Boot” in New York Post, January 1977 (Box 46, Folder 15.)
    - 1977 (Box 46, Folder 16.)
    - 1978 (Box 46, Folder 17.)
    - press releases, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 18.)
  - Personal – Articles about Julian Goodman
    - March 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1.)
    - April 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2.)
    - retirement, May 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3.)
    - retirement, June 1979 (Box 47, Folder 4.)
    - retirement, June 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5.)
    - July – November 1979 (Box 47, Folder 6.)
    - December 1979 (Box 47, Folder 7.)
    - tribute in Congressional Record, December 10, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 8.)
    - December 1979 (Box 47, Folder 9.)
    - 1980 (Box 47, Folder 10.)
    - 1981 -1986 (Box 47, Folder 11.)
    - Undated (Box 47, Folder 12.)
  - Personal – files by date
    - photocopy of the New York Times for the day JG went to work for NBC, June 30, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 13.)
    - 1948 -1953 (Box 47, Folder 14.)
    - White House News Conferences – confidential, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 15.)
    - 1950’s – undated (Box 47, Folder 16.)
    - 1954- 1956 (Box 47, Folder 17.)
    - 1956 (Box 47, Folder 18.)
    - 1957 (Box 47, Folder 19.)
  - Personal – files by date
    - Sigma Delta Chi (Professional Journalistic Fraternity, 1957 – 1972 (Box 48, Folder 1.)
    - 1958 (Box 48, Folder 2.)
    - JG appointed Director of News and Public Affairs at NBC, July 1959 (Box 48, Folder 3.)
    - 1962, Statement on the “obligation of NBC News” (Box 48, Folder 4.)
    - Employment documents, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 5.)
    - 1963- 1964 (Box 48, Folder 6.)
    - NBC progress report by Robert Kintner, December 1964 (Box 48, Folder 7.)
    - i.d. card – Senior Executive Vice President, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 8.)
    - JG becomes NBC President – letters, 1965 - 1966 (Box 48, Folder 9.)
    - Reception in Washington, D.C. for JG and Walter Scott, June 14, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 10.)
    - NBC employment contracts, 1966 – 1979 (Box 48, Folder 11.)
    - Committees declined, 1967 – 1978 (Box 48, Folder 12.)
    - trip to Europe to visit overseas staff – memo book, August 1967 (Box 48, Folder 13.)
    - 1968 (Box 48, Folder 14.)
    - London - House of Lords – luncheon menu, April 22, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 15.)
    - 1970 (Box 48, Folder 16.)
    - Business/personal travel, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 17.)
    - JG on “Enemies List” – Nixon and Watergate, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 18.)
    - requests, 1974 – 1975 (Box 48, Folder 19.)
    - Electronics, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 20.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 21.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 22.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 23.)
  - Personal – files by date
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong –preliminary planning, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 5.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong –preliminary planning, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 6.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong – itinerary and other, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 7.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 8.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 9.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 10.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 11.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 12.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 13.)
    - Trip to Japan, People’s Republic of China, and Hong Kong, July 1977 (Box 49, Folder 14.)
    - Election of Directors, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 15.)
    - JG Elected Chairman of NBC Executive Committee, September 1978 (Box 49, Folder 16.)
    - JG Elected Chairman of NBC Executive Committee, September 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17.)
    - JG Elected Chairman of NBC Executive Committee, September 1978 (Box 49, Folder 18.)
    - outline of duties of NBC Chairman, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 19.)
    - Gifts and acknowledgements, Christmas 1978 (Box 49, Folder 20.)
    - Business/personal travel, 1978- 1979 (Box 49, Folder 21.)
    - 1979 (Box 49, Folder 22.)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 23.)
  - Personal – Retirement, 1979
    - Press release, March 7, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 1.)
  - Personal – Retirement, 1979
    - January (Box 50, Folder 2.)
    - March 6 -7 (Box 50, Folder 3.)
    - March 8 (Box 50, Folder 4.)
    - March 9 (Box 50, Folder 5.)
    - March 10 – 12 (Box 50, Folder 6.)
    - March 13 -14 (Box 50, Folder 7.)
    - March 15 -16 (Box 50, Folder 8.)
    - March 19 (Box 50, Folder 9.)
    - March 20 - 26 (Box 50, Folder 10.)
  - Personal – Retirement, 1979
    - March 28 -30 (Box 51, Folder 1.)
    - April – August (Box 51, Folder 2.)
    - April – Re: book for Random House Publishers (Box 51, Folder 3.)
  - Personal – Retirement, 1979
    - Distinguished Service Award, March 28 (Box 51, Folder 4.)
    - Legal (Box 51, Folder 5.)
    - Legal (Box 51, Folder 6.)
  - Post Retirement
    - 1980 – 1984 (Box 51, Folder 7.)
    - 1985 – 1996 (Box 51, Folder 8.)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 51, Folder 9.)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 10.)
  - Personal – Appointment books
    - 1967 (Box 51, Folder 11.)
    - 1968 (Box 51, Folder 12.)
    - 1969 (Box 51, Folder 13.)
  - Personal – Appointment books
    - 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1.)
    - 1972 (Box 52, Folder 2.)
    - 1973 (Box 52, Folder 3.)
    - 1974 (Box 52, Folder 4.)
    - 1975 (Box 52, Folder 5.)
    - 1976 (Box 52, Folder 6.)
    - 1977 (Box 52, Folder 7.)
    - 1978 (Box 52, Folder 8.)
    - 1979 (Box 52, Folder 9.)
  - Personal – Appointment schedules
    - December 1977 – February 1978 (Box 53, Folder 1.)
    - March – April 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2.)
    - May – July 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3.)
    - August – November 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4.)
  - Personal – Telephone Message Register
    - December 23, 1977 – January 17, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 5.)
    - January 17 – February 9, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 6.)
    - February 10 – March 10, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 7.)
    - March 13 – April 26, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 8.)
    - April 27 – May 31, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 9.)
    - June 1 – June 14, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 10.)
    - June 15 – July 21, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 11.)
    - July 24 – August 18, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 12.)
    - August 21 – September 12, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 13.)
    - September 13 – October 12, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 14.)
    - October 13 – November 21, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 15.)
    - November 22 – December 29, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 16.)
  - Personal – Scrapbooks
    - #1-December 8, 1965 - January 23, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 1.)
    - #2 -March 7, 1966 - April 13, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 2.)
    - #3 -May 16, 1966 - May 30, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 3.)
  - Personal- Scrapbooks
    - #4 - July 2, 1966 - November 22, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 1.)
    - #5 - July 31, 1966 - October 21, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 2.)
    - #6 - October 2, 1966 - January 15, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 3.)
  - Personal – Scrapbooks
    - #7 - November 12, 1966 - January 1967 (Box 56, Folder 1.)
    - #8 - March 14, 1967 - May 26, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2.)
    - #9 - May 31, 1967 - June 1, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 3.)
    - #10 - July 19, 1967 - September 10, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 4.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #11 - October 7, 1967 - December 9, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 1.)
    - #12 - December 11, 1967 - April 17, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2.)
    - #13 - March 27, 1968 - August 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 3.)
    - #14 - August 13, 1968 - October 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 4.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #15 - November 18, 1968 - December 7, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 1.)
    - #16 - December 6, 1968 - March 17, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 2.)
    - #17 - March 13, 1969 - August 12, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook, April 23, 1969; London (Box 59, Folder 1.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #18 - August 9, 1969 - October 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1.)
    - #19 - December 30, 1969 - March 16, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 2.)
    - #20 - March 11, 1970 - May 26, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #21 - June 5, 1970 - August 25, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 1.)
    - #22 - September 1, 1970 - November 12, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 2.)
    - #23 - December 7, 1970 - April 5, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #24 - April 13, 1971 - June 8, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 1.)
    - #25 - July 5, 1971 - December 8, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2.)
    - #26 - January 1972 - March 1, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #27 - March 10, 1972 - March 28, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 1.)
    - #28 - May 17, 1972 - July 5, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 2.)
    - #29 - October 10, 1972 - November 30, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #30 - December 13, 1972 - January 18, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1.)
    - #31 - January 3, 1973 - March 23, 19873 (Box 64, Folder 2.)
    - #32 - May 7, 1973 - September 9, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #33 - July 4, 1973 - October 22, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 1.)
    - #34 - November 12, 1973 - January 21, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 2.)
    - #35 - February 6, 1974 - May 27, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #36 - April 1974 - October 20, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1.)
    - #37 - October 26, 1974 - May 12, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 2.)
    - #38 - March 14, 1975 - June 1, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #39 - May 13, 1976 - January 1, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 1.)
    - #40 - January 5, 1977 - May 18, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 2.)
    - #41 - May 23, 1977 - September 1977 (Box 67, Folder 3.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - #42 - November 10, 1977 - January 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1.)
    - #43 - January 23, 1978 - March 12, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2.)
  - Personal - Scrapbooks
    - The Chairman’s Dinner – Club “21” New York City, January 7, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1.)
    - The Chairman’s Dinner – Club “21” New York City, January 7, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2.)
- NBC Corporate - Programming
  - Programming
    - Children’s Programs, 1957 - 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 2.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1968; “Television for Preschool Children: a Proposal” (Box 70, Folder 3.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 4.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1970; Address by Julian Goodman (Box 70, Folder 5.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1970; Statement by Dr. Walter Menninger (Box 70, Folder 6.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 7.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 8.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 9.)
    - Children’s Programs, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 10.)
    - Churchill, Winston, Funeral - January 1965 (Box 70, Folder 11.)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 12.)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 13.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 14.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 15.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 16.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 17.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 18.)
    - Convention Hall floor plan, Democratic National Convention - 1964 (Box 70, Folder 19.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964; Directory (Box 70, Folder 20.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964; Press Releases (Box 70, Folder 21.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964; Schedule and Summary of Events (Box 70, Folder 22.)
  - Programming
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 1.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968; Daily credentials (Box 71, Folder 3.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 4.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 5.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 7.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 8.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 9.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 10.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 11.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 12.)
  - Programming
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 2.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 3.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; Acceptance speech of Jimmy Carter (Box 72, Folder 4.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; NBC News Convention Directory (Box 72, Folder 5.)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; NBC Convention Guide and Directory (Box 72, Folder 6.)
    - Elections, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 7.)
    - Elections, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 8.)
    - Elections, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 9.)
    - Elections, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 10.)
    - Elections, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 11.)
    - Elections, 1964; Network Election Service (Box 72, Folder 12.)
    - Elections, 1964; Network Election Service (Box 72, Folder 13.)
    - Elections, 1964; Network Election Service (Box 72, Folder 14.)
    - Elections, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 15.)
    - Elections, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 16.)
  - Programming
    - Elections, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 1.)
    - Elections, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2.)
    - Elections, 1968; Nixon – Humphrey Commercial Controversy (Box 73, Folder 3.)
    - Elections, 1968; NBC News supplement (Box 73, Folder 4.)
    - Elections, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5.)
    - Elections, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 6.)
    - Elections, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 7.)
    - Elections, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 8.)
    - Elections, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 9.)
    - Elections, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 10.)
    - Elections, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 11.)
    - The Equalizer – scripts (Box 73, Folder 12.)
    - The Equalizer – script, December 1985 (Box 73, Folder 13.)
    - First Tuesday, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 14.)
    - First Tuesday, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 15.)
    - First Tuesday /Chronolog, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 16.)
    - First Tuesday, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 17.)
    - The Godfather, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 18.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – March 28 – July 18 (Box 73, Folder 19.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – August 1 – August 31 (Box 73, Folder 20.)
  - Programming
    - Great Debates, 1960 – September 1 -21 (Box 74, Folder 1.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – September 22 -30 (Box 74, Folder 2.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – September 26; Transcript of First Joint Radio Television Broadcast of the debate between Senator John F. Kennedy and Vice President Richard M. Nixon (Box 74, Folder 3.)
    - Great Debates, 1960- October 4 – 5 (Box 74, Folder 4.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – October 6 -7 (Box 74, Folder 5.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – October 7; unofficial transcript of the Second Joint Radio Television Broadcast of the debate between Vice President Richard M. Nixon and Senator John F. Kennedy (Box 74, Folder 6.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – October 7; opening remarks (Box 74, Folder 7.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – October 8; telegrams to Kennedy and Nixon (Box 74, Folder 8.)
    - Great Debates, 1960- October 8 – 17 (Box 74, Folder 9.)
    - Great Debates, 1960- October 18-26 (Box 74, Folder 10.)
    - Great Debates, 1960- October 27 -31 (Box 74, Folder 11.)
  - Programming
    - Great Debates, 1960 – November 1 – December 9 (Box 75, Folder 1.)
    - Great Debates, 1960 – February – May 1961 (Box 75, Folder 2.)
    - Huntley-Brinkley Report, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 3.)
    - Huntley-Brinkley Report, 1966 – 67 (Box 75, Folder 4.)
    - Huntley – Brinkley Report, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 5.)
    - Huntley – Brinkley Report, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 6.)
    - Inauguration, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 7.)
    - Inauguration, 1973; booklet (Box 75, Folder 8.)
    - Inauguration, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 9.)
    - Inauguration, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 10.)
    - Issues and Answers (Box 75, Folder 11.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Administration, 1961-63 (Box 75, Folder 12.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Administration, 1961-63 (Box 75, Folder 13.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Administration, 1961-63 (Box 75, Folder 14.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. –European coverage, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 15.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 16.)
  - Programming
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 1.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 2.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 3.)
    - Kennedy, President John F. – “The Assassination of President John F. Kennedy- 1963” NBC Report (Box 76, Folder 4.)
    - “Seventy Hours and Thirty Minutes”, Kennedy, President John F. – Assassination – 1963 (Box 76, Folder 5.)
    - Kennedy, Senator Robert F. – Assassination, June 1968 (Box 76, Folder 6.)